## **DUKYUNG KANG**

#### **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

Email: grimgrim0522@gmail.com Website: dukyungkassia.site Phone: +82) 010.2362.8754

Graphic designer with 3 years of experience in motion and production design, specializing in visual storytelling. Adept at simplifying complex ideas through clear visuals, she brings strong collaboration and communication skills to projects that aim to inform and engage diverse audiences.

#### **EDUCATION**

# 2016.08~2020.05 Maryland Institute College of Art

## **Bachelor of Fine Arts**

Major in Graphic Design / Illustration Concentration

Cum Laude Honors Dean's List 2018~2020

Presidential Scholarship Awarded

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## 2023.01~2023.10 Assistant Production Designer

## A:WE

Working as a production designer of K-pop music and commercial videos, I assisted set-design, created main props, and designed graphic works.

#### 2021.08~2022.12

## **Motion Designer**

## **MBC (Munhwa Broadcasting Corporation)**

### **D.Content Creation Team**

Working as a graphic designer of '14F' Youtue channel, I branded various programs under the channel. I created title sequence, thumbnail, and motion graphics. I also produced commercial videos and designed merchandises.

## **SKILLS**

## Critical Thinking Visualizing Communication Leadership

2021.03~2021.07

## Producer Cocoon9

#### **Production Team**

I mostly did video editing and created motion graphics for commercial videos. I led film VFX projects, called 'Hey, Mammons' and 'Dingdong Challenge.'

#### **SOFTWARES**

## **ADOBE**

(Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects, Premiere Pro, Indesign, Audition)

C4D DSLR BLENDER SKETCHUP 2020.09~2020.12

# Designer MNET (Music Network)

### **Music Strategy and Development Team**

Part of the 'Kcon' concert team, I mostly worked on video editing and designed marketing digital images. Also, I participated as an on-set assistance.